<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tokyo Guide</string>

    <!-- Names of the categories -->
    <string name="category_visit">Visit</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shop</string>
    <string name="category_fun">Fun</string>
    <string name="category_eat">Eat</string>


    <!-- Text for VISIT category-->
    <string name="visit_item1_name">Tokyo Tower</string>
    <string name="visit_item1_description">
        \"Tokyo Tower (東京タワー Tōkyō tawā) is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen
        district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres (1,092 ft), it is the second-tallest structure
        in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and
        international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
        \n \n Built in 1958, the tower\'s main sources of income are tourism and antenna leasing.
        Over 150 million people have visited the tower. FootTown, a four-story building directly
        under the tower, houses museums, restaurants and shops. Departing from there, guests can visit
        two observation decks. The two-story Main Observatory is at 150 metres (490 ft), while the
        smaller Special Observatory reaches a height of 249.6 metres (819 ft).
        \n \n The tower acts as a support structure for an antenna. Intended for television broadcasting,
        radio antennas were installed in 1961, but the tower now broadcasts signals for Japanese media
        outlets such as NHK, TBS and Fuji TV. Japan\'s planned digital television transition by July
        2011 was problematic, however; Tokyo Tower\'s height, 332.9 m (1,092 ft) was not high enough
        to support complete terrestrial digital broadcasting to the area. A taller digital broadcasting
        tower, known as Tokyo Skytree, was completed on 29 February 2012. Every 5 years Tokyo Tower
        is repainted. It takes 1 year to repaint it.
        \n \n Since its completion in 1958, Tokyo Tower has become a prominent landmark in the city,
        and frequently appears in media set in Tokyo.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="visit_item1_information">
        Address:
        \n 4 Chome-2-8 Shibakoen, Minato, Tokyo, 105-0011
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Main Deck (150m) 9:00-23:00 (Last admission 22:30)
        \n Top Deck Tour (250m) Every 15 minutes between 09:00 and 22:15 (Last Tour 22:15)
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.tokyotower.co.jp/en.html
    </string>

    <string name="visit_item2_name">Tsukiji Market</string>
    <string name="visit_item2_description">
        \"The Tsukiji Market (築地市場 Tsukiji shijō), supervised by the Tokyo Metropolitan Central
        Wholesale Market (東京都中央卸売市場 Tōkyō-to Chūō Oroshiuri Shijō) of the Tokyo Metropolitan
        Bureau of Industrial and Labor Affairs, is the biggest wholesale fish and seafood market in
        the world and also one of the largest wholesale food markets of any kind.
        \n \n The market is located in Tsukiji in central Tokyo, between the Sumida River and the
        upmarket Ginza shopping district. While the inner wholesale market has restricted access to
        visitors, the outer retail market, restaurants, and associated restaurant supply stores remain
        a major tourist attraction for both domestic and overseas visitors.[1][2]\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="visit_item2_information">
        Address:
        \n 5 Chome-2-1 Tsukiji, Chūō, Tokyo, 104-0045
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Tuna Auction 3:30am - 6:00am (2 tours, you need to arrive early to reserve your spot)
        \n 9:00am - 2:00pm (Many shops are closed on Sunday and Wednesday)
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.tsukiji.or.jp/english/
    </string>

    <string name="visit_item3_name">Edo-Tokyo Museum</string>
    <string name="visit_item3_description">
        \"The Edo-Tokyo Museum (江戸東京博物館 Edo Tōkyō Hakubutsukan) is a museum of the history of
        Tokyo during the Edo period.[2] It was established in 1993. The main features of the permanent
        exhibitions are the life-size replica of the Nihonbashi, which was the bridge leading into
        Edo; the Nakamuraza theatre; and scale models of towns and buildings from the Edo, Meiji and
        Shōwa periods. The museum is adjacent to the Ryōgoku Kokugikan. It was designed by Kiyonori
        Kikutake.[3] The distinctive elevated shape of the museum building is modelled after an old
        storehouse in the kurazukuri style.
        \n \n The Edo-Tokyo Open Air Architectural Museum is a branch of the Edo-Tokyo Museum.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="visit_item3_information">
        Address:
        \n 1 Chome-4-1 Yokoami, Sumida, Tokyo, 130-0015
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 9:30 - 17:30 (Saturday：9:30 - 19:30)
        \n ※ Entry is permitted until 30 minutes before closing
        \n Closed on Monday.
        \n When a national holiday or its substitute falls on a Monday, the Museum is OPEN and is
        closed on the following day.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.edo-tokyo-museum.or.jp/en/
    </string>

    <string name="visit_item4_name">Meiji Shrine</string>
    <string name="visit_item4_description">
        \"Meiji Shrine (明治神宮 Meiji Jingū), located in Shibuya, Tokyo, is the Shinto shrine that is
        dedicated to the deified spirits of Emperor Meiji and his wife, Empress Shōken.[1][2] The
        shrine does not contain the emperor\'s grave, which is located at Fushimi-momoyama, south of Kyoto.
        \n \n [&#8230;] Meiji Shrine is located in a forest that covers an area of 70 hectares (170
        acres). This area is covered by an evergreen forest that consists of 120,000 trees of 365
        different species, which were donated by people from all parts of Japan when the shrine was
        established. The forest is visited by many as a recreation and relaxation area in the center
        of Tokyo.[2] The entrance to the shrine complex leads through the Jingu Bashi bridge.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="visit_item4_information">
        Address:
        \n 1-1 Yoyogikamizonocho, Shibuya, Tokyo, 151-8557
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Meiji Jingu opens with sunrise and closes with sunset, the opening hours change every
        month. Please check the official website.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.meijijingu.or.jp/english/about/1.html
    </string>

    <string name="visit_item5_name">Tokyo National Museum</string>
    <string name="visit_item5_description">
        \"The Tokyo National Museum (東京国立博物館 Tōkyō Kokuritsu Hakubutsukan), or TNM, established in
        1872, is the oldest Japanese national museum,[2] the largest art museum in Japan and one of
        the largest art museums in the world. The museum collects, houses, and preserves a comprehensive
        collection of art works and archaeological objects of Asia, focusing on Japan. The museum holds
        over 110,000 objects, which includes 87 Japanese National Treasure holdings and 610 Important
        Cultural Property holdings (as of July 2005). The museum also conducts research and organizes
        educational events related to its collection.
        \n \n The museum is located inside Ueno Park in Taitō, Tokyo. The facilities consist of the
        Honkan (本館, Japanese Gallery), Tōyōkan (東洋館, Asian Gallery), Hyōkeikan (表慶館), Heiseikan
        (平成館), Hōryū-ji Hōmotsukan (法隆寺宝物館, the Gallery of Hōryū-ji Treasures), as well as Shiryōkan
        (資料館, the Research and Information Center), and other facilities. There are restaurants and
        shops within the museum\'s premises, as well as outdoor exhibitions (including the Kuromon)
        and a garden where visitors can enjoy seasonal views.
        \n \n The museum\'s collections focus on ancient Japanese art and Asian art along the Silk
        Road. There is also a large collection of Greco-Buddhist art.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="visit_item5_information">
        Address:
        \n 13-9 Uenokoen, Taitō, Tokyo, 110-8712
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 9:30 - 17:00 (last admission at 16:30)
        \n Open until 21:00 on Fridays and Saturdays.
        \n Last admission 30 minutes before closing.
        \n Closed on Mondays and year-end holidays.
        \n (open on Mondays that fall on national holidays, in which case the museum is closed on following day)
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.tnm.jp/?lang=en
    </string>

    <string name="visit_item6_name">Roppongi Hills</string>
    <string name="visit_item6_description">
        \"Roppongi Hills (六本木ヒルズ Roppongi Hiruzu) is a development project in Tokyo and one of
        Japan\'s largest integrated property developments, located in the Roppongi district of Minato,
        Tokyo. The architecture and use of the space is documented in the book Six Strata: Roppongi Hills Redefined.[3]
        \n \n Constructed by building tycoon Minoru Mori, the mega-complex incorporates office space,
        apartments, shops, restaurants, cafés, movie theatres, a museum, a hotel, a major TV studio,
        an outdoor amphitheatre, and a few parks. The centerpiece is the 54-story Mori Tower. Mori\'s
        stated vision was to build an integrated development where high-rise inner-urban communities
        allow people to live, work, play, and shop in proximity to eliminate commuting time. He argued
        that this would increase leisure time, quality of life, and benefit Japan\'s national competitiveness.
        Seventeen years after the design\'s initial conception, the complex opened to the public on April 25, 2003.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="visit_item6_information">
        Address:
        \n 6 Chome-11-1 Roppongi, Minato, Tokyo, 106-6108
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Varies depending on which part of Roppongi Hills you are planning to visit.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.roppongihills.com/en/
    </string>


    <!-- Text for SHOP category-->
    <string name="shop_item1_name">Harajuku</string>
    <string name="shop_item1_description">
        \"Harajuku is known internationally as a center of Japanese youth culture and fashion.[2]
        Shopping and dining options include many small, youth-oriented, independent boutiques and
        cafés, but the neighborhood also attracts many larger international chain stores with high-end
        luxury merchandisers extensively represented along Omotesando.
        \n \n Harajuku Station on the JR East Yamanote Line and Meiji-jingumae \'Harajuku\' Station
        served by the Tokyo Metro Chiyoda Line and Tokyo Metro Fukutoshin Line also act as gateways
        to local attractions such as the Meiji Shrine, Yoyogi Park and Yoyogi National Gymnasium, making
        Harajuku and its environs one of the most popular destinations in Tokyo for both domestic and
        international tourists.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia, GoTokyo)
    </string>
    <string name="shop_item1_information">
        Address:
        \n \"Harajuku is the common name given to a geographic area spreading from Harajuku
        Station to Omotesando, corresponding on official maps of Shibuya ward as Jingūmae 1 chōme to 4 chōme.
        In popular reference, Harajuku also encompasses many smaller backstreets such as Takeshita
        Street and Cat Street spreading from Sendagaya in the north to Shibuya in the south.\"
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Most shops opens around 10:00am and closes around 7:00pm to 8:00pm.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.gotokyo.org/en/destinations/western-tokyo/harajuku/
    </string>

    <string name="shop_item2_name">Shibuya</string>
    <string name="shop_item2_description">
        \"Shibuya (渋谷区 Shibuya-ku), literally "Astringent Valley", is a special ward in Tokyo, Japan.
        A major commercial and business centre, it houses the two busiest railway stations in the world,
        Shinjuku Station (southern half) and Shibuya Station.
        \n \n As of May 1, 2016, it has an estimated population of 221,801 and a population density
        of 14,679.09 people per km2 (38,018.7/sq mi). The total area is 15.11 km2 (5.83 sq mi).
        \n \n The name "Shibuya" is also used to refer to the shopping district which surrounds
        Shibuya Station, one of Tokyo\'s busiest railway stations. This area is known as one of the
        fashion centers of Japan, particularly for young people, and as a major nightlife area.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia, GoTokyo)
    </string>
    <string name="shop_item2_information">
        Address:
        \n All the area around Shibuya Station.
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Most shops opens around 10:00am and closes around 7:00pm to 8:00pm.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.gotokyo.org/en/destinations/western-tokyo/shibuya/
    </string>

    <string name="shop_item3_name">Ginza</string>
    <string name="shop_item3_description">
        (Ginza)\"is a popular upscale shopping area of Tokyo, with numerous internationally
        renowned department stores, boutiques, restaurants and coffeehouses located in its vicinity.
        It is considered one of the most expensive, elegant, and luxurious streets in the world.
        \n \n Ginza was a part of the old Kyobashi ward of Tokyo City, which, together with Nihonbashi and
        Kanda, formed the core of Shitamachi[1], the original downtown center of Edo-Tokyo, before
        the rise of newer secondary centers such as Shinjuku and Shibuya.
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia, GoTokyo)
    </string>
    <string name="shop_item3_information">
        Address:
        \n \"Ginza is a district of Chūō, Tokyo, located south of Yaesu and Kyōbashi, west of
        Tsukiji, east of Yūrakuchō and Uchisaiwaichō, and north of Shinbashi.\"
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Most shops opens around 10:00am and closes around 7:00pm to 8:00pm.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.gotokyo.org/en/destinations/central-tokyo/ginza/
    </string>

    <string name="shop_item4_name">Shimokitazawa</string>
    <string name="shop_item4_description">
        \"Shimokitazawa (下北沢 Shimokitazawa) is a commercial and entertainment district in Setagaya,
        Tokyo. Also known as "Shimokita", the neighbourhood is well known for the density of small
        independent fashion retailers, cafes, theaters, bars and live music venues.\"
        \n \"The neighbourhood is often compared with the backstreets of Ura-Harajuku and Koenji; smaller
        shop units and restricted vehicular access has limited its appeal to larger domestic and
        international fashion merchandisers, enabling independent retailers to survive.
        \n [&#8230;]The neighbourhood has long been a center for stage theater and live music venues;
        serves as a home to the historic Honda Gekijō theater and holds theatre festivals throughout
        the year. With numerous cafes, secondhand and vintage fashion and recorded music outlets,
        Shimokitazawa remains popular with students and followers of Japanese youth subcultures.[1]\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia, GoTokyo)
    </string>
    <string name="shop_item4_information">
        Address:
        \n \"The district consists of the streets immediately surrounding Shimo-Kitazawa Station,
        where the Odakyu Electric Railway and Keio Inokashira Lines intersect.\"
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Most shops opens around 10:00am and closes around 7:00pm to 8:00pm.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.gotokyo.org/en/tourists/areas/areamap/shimokitazawa.html
    </string>

    <string name="shop_item5_name">Tokyu Hands</string>
    <string name="shop_item5_description">
        \"Tokyu Hands Inc., known as Tokyu Hands (東急ハンズ Tōkyū Hanzu), is a Japanese department
        store. Tokyu Hands is part of the Tokyu Department Store (itself a member of the Tokyu Group), its
        first store opened in Shibuya, Tokyo in 1976.[1] Tokyu Hands got its start as a DIY (Do-It-Yourself)
        store, hence the logo with two hands, and the emphasis on crafts and materials for projects.
        \n \n [&#8230;] Tokyu Hands focuses on hobby, home improvement and lifestyle products. At the
        Shibuya flagship store, products include toys, games, novelty items, gift cards, gift wrap,
        costumes, bicycles, travel products (such as luggage and camping gear), hobby materials,
        household hardware, tools, do-it-yourself kits, pet supplies, office supplies and stationery;
        calligraphy, painting, drawing supplies, furniture, lighting, home appliances, and
        storage solutions.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="shop_item5_information">
        Address:
        \n Times Square Building 2-8F, 5-24-2 Sendagaya, Shibuya-ku, Tokyo, 151-0051
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 10:00 - 20:00
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.tokyu-hands.co.jp/en/list/shinjuku/
    </string>

    <string name="shop_item6_name">Don Quijote</string>
    <string name="shop_item6_description">
        \"Don Quijote (ドン・キホーテ Don Kihōte) is a discount chain store that has over 160 locations
        throughout Japan, three stores in Hawaii and one in Singapore.[2][3] It carries a wide range
        of products, from basic groceries to electronics to clothing. The store is well known in
        Japan and is often referred to by its shortened name Donki (ドンキ). Distinctly, Don Quijote
        tends to keep very late hours for Japanese retailing (to 3 or 5am, or even 24 hours) and it
        packs its goods from ceiling to floor in a distinct merchandising strategy.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="shop_item6_information">
        Address:
        \n 28-6 Udagawa-cho, Shibuya-ku, Tokyo, 150-0042
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Open 24/24h.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.donki.com/en/?pre=le
    </string>


    <!-- Text for FUN category-->
    <string name="fun_item1_name">Odaiba</string>
    <string name="fun_item1_description">
        \"An ultramodern area for residents and businesses alike, the Odaiba district is your go-to place
        for pleasure cruising, shopping and general seaside fun. The manmade island built in Tokyo Bay
        was originally created by the Edo shogunate (1603-1867) to protect Tokyo from the threat of
        marine attacks. Today it serves a very different purpose—as an entertainment hub for the
        entire family. Set aside a full day for maximum enjoyment.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia, GoTokyo)
    </string>
    <string name="fun_item1_information">
        Address:
        \n \"You can reach Odaiba on the Yurikamome Line at the stations of Odaiba-Kaihinkoen,
        Daiba, Fune-no-Kagakukan, Telecom Center and Aomi. You can also get to the area from the
        Rinkai Line\'s Tokyo Teleport Station. To board the water bus, head to Odaiba Seaside
        Park Pier, which is around five minutes from Daiba and Odaiba-kaihinkoen stations. \"
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Varies depending on which part of Odaiba you are planning to visit.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.gotokyo.org/en/destinations/southern-tokyo/odaiba/
    </string>

    <string name="fun_item2_name">Hanayashiki</string>
    <string name="fun_item2_description">
        \"Hanayashiki (浅草花やしき Asakusa hanayashiki) is an amusement park in Asakusa, Taitō,
        Tokyo[1] that has operated since 1853. It is operated by Hanayashiki Co., Ltd., a
        subsidiary of Bandai Namco Holdings. It is claimed to be the oldest amusement park in Japan.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="fun_item2_information">
        Address:
        \n 2-28-1 Asakusa Taito-ku Tokyo, 111-0032
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 10:00 - 18:00
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.hanayashiki.net/en
    </string>

    <string name="fun_item3_name">Tokyo Disneyland</string>
    <string name="fun_item3_description">
        \"Tokyo Disneyland (東京ディズニーランド Tōkyō Dizunīrando) is a 115-acre (47 ha) theme park at
        the Tokyo Disney Resort in Urayasu, Chiba Prefecture, Japan, near Tokyo.[1] Its main gate is
        directly adjacent to both Maihama Station and Tokyo Disneyland Station. It was the first Disney
        park to be built outside the United States, and it opened on 15 April 1983. The park was constructed
        by Walt Disney Imagineering in the same style as Disneyland in California and Magic Kingdom
        in Florida.[1] It is owned by The Oriental Land Company, which licenses the theme from The Walt
        Disney Company. Tokyo Disneyland and its companion park, Tokyo DisneySea, are the only Disney
        parks not wholly or partly owned by the Walt Disney Company (however, Disney has creative control).
        \n The park has seven themed areas: the World Bazaar; the four traditional Disney lands:
        Adventureland, Westernland, Fantasyland and Tomorrowland; and two mini-lands: Critter Country
        and Mickey\'s Toontown. Many of these areas mirror those in the original Disneyland as they are
        based on American Disney films and fantasies. Fantasyland includes Peter Pan\'s Flight, Snow
        White\'s Scary Adventures, Dumbo the Flying Elephant, based on Disney films and characters.[2]
        The park is noted for its extensive open spaces, to accommodate the large crowds that visit
        the park.[1] In 2013, Tokyo Disneyland hosted 17.2 million visitors, making it the world\'s
        second-most visited theme park behind the Magic Kingdom at Walt Disney World Resort.[3]\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="fun_item3_information">
        Address:
        \n 1-1 Maihama, Urayasu, Chiba Prefecture, 279-0031
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 8:00 - 22:00
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.tokyodisneyresort.jp/en/tdl/
    </string>

    <string name="fun_item4_name">Ghibli Museum</string>
    <string name="fun_item4_description">
        \"The Ghibli Museum (三鷹の森ジブリ美術館 Mitaka no Mori Jiburi Bijutsukan, Mitaka Forest Ghibli
        Museum) is a museum showcasing the work of the Japanese animation studio Studio Ghibli. It is
        located in Inokashira Park in Mitaka, a western city of Tokyo, Japan. The museum combines
        features of a children\'s museum, technology museum, and a fine arts museum, and is dedicated
        to the art and technique of animation. Some features include a replica of the Catbus from My
        Neighbor Totoro (1988), a café, bookstore, rooftop garden, and a theater for exclusive short
        films by Studio Ghibli.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="fun_item4_information">
        Address:
        \n 1-1-83 Simorenjaku, Mitaka-shi, Tokyo, 181-0013
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 10:00 - 18:00
        \n Please note that all admission is by advance reservation only. No tickets are sold at the Museum.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.ghibli-museum.jp/en/
    </string>

    <string name="fun_item5_name">Miraikan</string>
    <string name="fun_item5_description">
        \"The National Museum of Emerging Science and Innovation (日本科学未来館 Nippon Kagaku
        Mirai-kan), simply known as the Miraikan (未来館, literally \"Future Museum\"), is a museum
        created by Japan\'s Science and Technology Agency.\"
        \n \"Some highlights include real-time displays of data from a huge array of seismometers across
        Japan which shows the country gently vibrating. The occasional earthquakes for which Japan is
        noted show up as larger movements. Visitors can search the on-line database of recent earthquake activity.
        \n A section of rock core taken across the Cretaceous–Paleogene boundary (K–T boundary) records a
        major meteorite impact event that is believed to have led to the final demise of the dinosaurs.
        Asimo, the Honda[1] robot is one of the star attractions along with the model maglev train.\"
        \"Every year between three and six specially curated exhibitions are produced and shown, with
        science and art often overlapping. They dealt with a wide range of topics from \"Toilet -
        Human Waste and Earth\'s Future\" to the \"Making of the Tokyo Sky Tree\" and \"Terminator
        Exhibition - Battle or Coexistence? Robots and Our Future\".[7] In 2012 the special exhibition
        \"The Story of the End of the World: 73 Questions We Must Answer\" dealt with the Tohoku earthquake
        and its aftermath.[8]
        \n Multilingual staff conduct demonstrations about leading edge Japanese science.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="fun_item5_information">
        Address:
        \n 2-3-6 Aomi, Koto, Tokyo, 135-0064
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 10:00 - 17:00 (Closed on Tuesday)
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.miraikan.jst.go.jp/en/
    </string>

    <string name="fun_item6_name">Tokyo Dome City</string>
    <string name="fun_item6_description">
        \"Tokyo Dome City (東京ドームシティ Tōkyō Dōmu Shiti), referred to as Big Egg City before January
        1, 2000, is an entertainment complex in Bunkyo, Tokyo, Japan.
        \n It includes the world\'s largest roofed baseball stadium known as Tokyo Dome (nicknamed
        \"Big Egg\"), an amusement park known as Tokyo Dome City Attractions (formerly Kōrakuen
        Yūenchi), and Korakuen Hall. In May 2003, a spa resort known as LaQua opened for business near
        Tokyo Dome City Attractions. It also hosts character shows for Toei Company\'s Toei Superheroes,
        including the Kamen Rider and Super Sentai series.
        \n The Tokyo Dome City contains the Tokyo Dome Hotel, a 43-story hotel that is easily
        visible from the street and from the Tokyo Subway Suidobashi Station, which is only two blocks away.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: Wikipedia)
    </string>
    <string name="fun_item6_information">
        Address:
        \n 1 Chome-3-61 Koraku, Bunkyō, Tokyo, 112-0004
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Varies depending on which part of Tokyo Dome City you are planning to visit.
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.tokyo-dome.co.jp/en/tourists/
    </string>


    <!-- Text for EAT category-->
    <string name="eat_item1_name">Maid Café</string>
    <string name="eat_item1_description">
        \"Maid cafés (メイド喫茶 / メイドカフェ Meido kissa / Meido kafe) are a subcategory of cosplay
        restaurants found predominantly in Japan. In these cafés, waitresses dressed in maid costumes
        act as servants, and treat customers as masters (and mistresses) in a private home, rather
        than as café patrons. The first permanent[1] maid café, Cure Maid Café, was established in
        Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan, in March 2001,[2] but maid cafés are becoming increasingly popular.\"
        \n \"Most maid cafés offer menus similar to those of more typical cafés. Customers can
        order coffee, other beverages, and a wide variety of entrées and desserts. However, in maid
        cafés, waitresses will often decorate a customer\’s order with cute designs at his or her
        table. Syrup can be used to decorate desserts, and omelette rice (オムライス Omu-raisu), a popular
        entrée, is typically decorated using ketchup.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text: Wikipedia / image: s.wsj.net/)
    </string>
    <string name="eat_item1_information">
        Address:
        \n Mitsuwa Bld. 4F - 7F, Sotokanda 1-11-4, Chiyoda, Tokyo, 101-0021
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Weekday  11:30～22:00 / Saturday  10:30～22:00
        \n Sunday and Holiday  10:30～22:00
        \n Last Order  FOOD 20:50 / DRINKS 21:20
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.cafe-athome.com/en/
    </string>

    <string name="eat_item2_name">Kichijoji Yurei</string>
    <string name="eat_item2_description">
        \"Japan is known for the country of horror after producing such movies as the Ring or the
        Grudge so why not to throw yourself into a scary bit in Japan! Well, the ghost restaurant is
        not as scary as those movies but more like a fun place! The restaurant has unique ghost themed
        menu, ghost like dressed waiters and few surprises might pop up while you dine!\"
        \n \n (Copyright text: jw-webmagazine.com / image: tofugu.com)
    </string>
    <string name="eat_item2_information">
        Address:
        \n 1–8–11 Kichijoji Minamicho, Musashino-city, Tokyo, 180-0003
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 17:00 - 01:00
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.yurei.jp/ (Japanese)
    </string>

    <string name="eat_item3_name">Robot Restaurant</string>
    <string name="eat_item3_description">
        \"When in Tokyo, don\'t miss an evening of awesome entertainment at the Robot Restaurant.
        Located in the Kabukicho red-light district, Robot Restaurant puts on an eclectic 1-hour cabaret
        show with performances full of flashing lights, taiko drums, and techno music. Your entry ticket
        includes one drink of your choice to sip on as you experience a fun, and sometimes campy,
        neon-lit show where glitzy ladies dance with dinosaurs, ninjas, a giant panda, and (of course)
        robots.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text: viator.com / image: travelcaffeine.com)</string>
    <string name="eat_item3_information">
        Address:
        \n 1-7-1 Kabukicho Shinjuku-ku Tokyo, Japan, 160-0021
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 16:00 - 23:00
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.shinjuku-robot.com/pc/index.php?lng=en
    </string>

    <string name="eat_item4_name">Kawaii Monster Cafe</string>
    <string name="eat_item4_description">
        \"Kawaii Monster Cafe in Harajuku, Tokyo, opened in the summer of 2015 under the concept of
        \"swallowing everything around the fashion mecca like a monster\" and represents a
        distinctively new approach to pop-art and dining. The cafe was born as a creation of the widely
        acclaimed modern art designer Sebastian Masuda who fascinates the world with his peculiar take
        on \"kawaii\" (cuteness). Having previously worked on the music videos of the famous J-pop
        star Kyary Pamyu Pamyu, Sebastian Masuda incorporated his edgy vision of art and fashion into
        a flashy colourful interior that suits the concept of engulfing the trendiest urban cultures
        in Tokyo.
        \n \n Visitors enter the Kawaii Monster Cafe through the mouth of a giant monster and find
        themselves inside a gaudy space of glitter, clashing colours and unique design. Lovers of
        contemporary pop-art will be thrilled to discover edgy installations such as the cake-shaped
        merry-go-round, and will continue to explore the different areas of this crazy cafe:
        \n - Mushroom Disco, a space in which giant poisonous mushrooms coexist with colourful
        candies as part of the interior.
        \n - Milk Stand, where cute but slightly twisted figures of animals drink from baby milk
        bottles.
        \n - Bar Experiment, the deep sea world surrounded by glowing jellyfish tentacles.
        \n - Mel-Tea Room, where ants lead the guests to melting ice cream and sweets.

        \n \n The food and drinks served here complement the wacky interior and guarantee that guests
        will have an unforgettable dining experience of fashion and art.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text: govoyagin.com / image: timeout.com)
    </string>
    <string name="eat_item4_information">
        Address:
        \n 4-31-10 Jingumae, Shibuya-ku, Tokyo 150-0001
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n 11:30 - 22:30 (last entry 21:30)
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://kawaiimonster.jp/
        \n \n Official ticket reservation website:
        \n https://www.govoyagin.com/activities/japan-tokyo-reservation-for-kawaii-monster-cafe-official-partner/4138
        </string>

    <string name="eat_item5_name">Ninja Restaurant</string>
    <string name="eat_item5_description">
        \"Visit this ninja-themed izakaya in present day Tokyo which lets you experience dining inside
        a ninja mansion, complete with the perfect Japanese ninja era atmosphere. The restaurant\'s
        interior involve cave-like passageways, bridges, ponds, and gardens. Enjoy not only their menu
        and alcoholic beverages, but also the hospitality and good customer service of their waiters
        dressed in ninja attires. Every customer will surely feel being back to the former centuries
        as the ninja waiters cater to their orders while role-playing as actual ninjas by the sides.
        \n NINJA AKASAKA\'s feature their signature ninja-inspired courses which include Shuriken
        star-blades grissini, Mont Blanc of vegetables, chicken fritter ninja-style, special stone-boiled
        soup, etc. Being famous for a very tourist-friendly restaurant in Tokyo, they also have limited
        courses such as vegetarian course, and pork and alcohol-free courses for customers who have
        limited food choices, but would still like to enjoy the ninja experience at NINJA AKASAKA.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text and image: triplelights.com)
    </string>
    <string name="eat_item5_information">
        Address:
        \n Tokyu plaza Akasaka 1F, 2-14-3, Nagatacho, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo, 100-0014
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Monday to Saturday 17:00 - 1:00 (Door closes at 22:30)
        \n Sunday and Holiday: 17:00 - 23:00 (Door closes at 21:45)
        \n \n Official website:
        \n http://www.ninjaakasaka.com/
    </string>

    <string name="eat_item6_name">Kyomachi Koishigure</string>
    <string name="eat_item6_description">
        \"Visiting Tokyo but you can\'t quite make it out to Kyoto? Kyomachi Koi Shigure is an
        izakaya where the theme is the town of Kyoto! As soon as you enter, there\'s a replica bridge
        you can cross to step into the old capital of Japan. All around you are beautiful fall leaves
        (since it\'s said to be the best season in Kyoto), and the red bridge looks beautiful in the
        autumnal atmosphere—it\'s also a popular photo spot!
        \n In another area, you can see water running down like a spring, creating a small river.
        \n Walking around the izakaya really feels like exploring the historic back alleys of
        Kyoto! Maybe this one isn\'t so much \"weird\" as \"cool\", but surely visiting Kyoto in
        Tokyo is a bit of an odd (if awesome) choice.\"
        \n \n (Copyright text: allabout-japan.com / image: tokyogirlsupdate.com)
    </string>
    <string name="eat_item6_information">
        Address:
        \n Musashino Building 6F, 3-27-10, Shinjuku, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo, 160-0022
        \n \n Opening time:
        \n Monday and Sunday: 17:00 - 23:00
        \n Tuesday to Saturday, and before holiday: 17:00 - 4:00
        \n \n Official website:
        \n https://www.dd-holdings.jp/shops/kyomachikoisigure/shinjyuku (Japanese)
    </string>


</resources>
